Hill, James C. Arbitration Files 5538
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II - Arbitration Files
  - Sub-Series B. Arbitration Files
    - Publishers Association of New York City (Daily News) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 12)
      5/11/1960; Issue: Contracting Out.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (Daily News) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 13)
      7/26/1960; Issues: Compensation; Medical Insurance; Vacations.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (Daily News) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 14)
      6/15/60; No Decision.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (Grand Central Terminal) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 15)
      9/9/1960; Issue: Jurisdiction.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (Long Island Daily Press) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 16)
      12/6/1960; Issue: Working Conditions.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (Long Island Railroad) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 17)
      7/1/60; Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Mirror) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 18)
      9/26/1960; Issue: Evaluation of Job Factors.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Post) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 19)
      12/3/1960; Issue: Employer - Union Relations.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 20)
      2/17/60; Issues: Suspension; Improper Work Practices.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      5/12/60. Issue: Evaluation of Job Factors.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      5/13/60; Issue: Duty to Bargain.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      5/20/1960; Settled.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      7/1/1960; Issue: Working Conditions.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      9/13/60; Settled.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      9/18/1960; Withdrawn.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      9/19/60; Postponed.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      9/21/1960; Opinion Missing.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      10/24/1960; Adjourned.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 10)
      11/15/1960; Withdrawn.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Times) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 11)
      12/6/1960; Issues: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit; Assignment of Jobs.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (Daily News) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 12)
      10/24/1960; Issue: Working Conditions.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (Daily News) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 13)
      10/29/1960; Issue: Equipment and Physical Facilities.
    - Publishers Association of New York City (Pennsylvania Railroad) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 14)
      8/30/1960; Issue: Working Conditions.
    - Publishers Association of New York City vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 15)
      6/60-12/60; Miscellaneous Cases.
    - Staten Island News Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1961 (Box 106, Folder 16)
      1/11/1961; Issues: Welfare Funds; Pension Funds.
    - Miscellaneous Agreements - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1958-1961 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Bulletins - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 18)
      January - April; October - November 1960.
    - Miscellaneous - List of Decisions Which Have Appeared in Published Report of B.N.A. and a Sampling of Other Decisions., 1960 (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - Pacific Greyhound Lines vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      4/15/73. Issues: Discharge; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs. Transport Workers Union of America, 1962 (Box 107, Folder 2)
      9/62; See Emergency Board Case with These Parties.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs. Flight Engineers International Association, Pan American Airways Chapter, 1962 (Box 107, Folder 3)
      10/10/1962; A-6245 Issue: Temporary Transfers.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs. Flight Engineers International Association, Pan American Airways Chapter, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 4)
      3/12/1963; Issue: Transfers.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs. Flight Engineers International Association, Pan American Airways Chapter, T.J. Swain and R.J. Racine, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 5)
      5/15/1965; Issue: Employee Rights.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs. Flight Engineers International Association, Pan American Airways Chapter, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      5/10/1965; #LAD-FE-63-1 Issues: Discrimination; Training and Trial Periods.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs. Flight Engineers International Association, Pan American Airways Chapter, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 7)
      8/11/1966; Issues: Recall; Compensation; Layoffs; Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppages.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs. Transport Workers Union of America, 1967 (Box 107, Folder 8)
      5/4/1967; A-7841 Issue: Schedules of Work.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs. Flight Engineers International Association, Pan American Airways Chapter, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 1)
      7/2/1967; Issue: Seniority.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs. Transport Workers Union of America, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 2)
      3/21/68; A-7841 Issue: Schedules of Work.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs. Airline Dispatchers Association, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 3)
      9/23/1969; #D-69-20-HNL Issues: Elimination of Jobs; Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Plume and Atwood Manufacturing Company vs. Thomaston Brass Workers Union, Local 62U, International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers - ca., 1960 (Box 108, Folder 4)
      7/19/60; Issues: Layoffs; Seniority.
    - Port Authority of Allegheny County vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 85. Arbitration Award and Proceedings Transcripts Currently on Loan to Mr. Hill. (Box 109-112, Folder All)
    - Publishers Association of New York City (New York Mirror) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      8/29/1960
    - Purex Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 2)
      10/8/74; #73-012 Resolved.
    - Quaker Oats Company vs. International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, Local 221, American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1963 (Box 114, Folder 1)
      5/7/1963; Issues: Bidding; Seniority.
    - R. & K. Baking Corporation vs. Bakery and Confectionery Workers of America, Local 3, 1958 (Box 114, Folder 2)
      4/17/1958; Arb.6095 Issues: Discharge; Incompetence and Inefficiency.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. Radio Communications Assemblers Union, 1959 (Box 114, Folder 3)
      6/1/1959; Issues: Suspension; Improper Personal Conduct.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. Radio Communications Assemblers Union., 1962 (Box 114, Folder 4)
      ca. 1/62. Opinion Missing
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 103, 1963 (Box 114, Folder 5)
      10/2/1963; Grievance #7694D Withdrawn.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 103, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 6)
      8/28//64; Grievance #57076 Withdrawn.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 103, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 7)
      6/16/1965; Grievance #94979 Case #L-46281-PHI-L-262-65 Settled.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 241, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      9/17/65; Grievance #91187 and 91188 Case #L- 45588 PHI-L-138-65 Withdrawn.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 9)
      10/12/1965; Grievance #47275 Case #L-45588 PHI-L-412-63 Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 676, 1966 (Box 114, Folder 10)
      4/26/1966; #14-30-0076-66 Withdrawn.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 241, 1967 (Box 114, Folder 11)
      2/17/67; Grievance #95384 Case #14-30-0268-66 Withdrawn.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. Association of Scientists and Professional Engineering Personnel, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 12)
      ca. 6/68; Grievance #102502 Case #14-30-0564-67 Withdrawn.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 241, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 13)
      3/6/1968; Grievance #60831 Case #14-30-0694- 67 Withdrawn.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. Association of Scientists and Professional Engineering Personnel, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 14)
      8/6/1968; Withdrawn.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 241, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 15)
      12/9/1968; Grievance #82091 Case #14-30-0781- 67 Issues: Merit Increases; Merit Review.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 241, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 15A)
      8/6/68; Grievance #97833 Case #14-30-0750-66 Withdrawn.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 106, 1969 (Box 114, Folder 16)
      9/24/1969; Grievance #74897 Case #14-30-0154-68 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - Radio Corporation of America vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1971 (Box 114, Folder 17)
      ca. 1971; #14-30-0943-71 Only 1 Sheet in Folder, with Names and Positions.
    - Railroads vs. Brotherhood of Railway Signalmen, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 18)
      4/3/1964; National Mediation Board Case #A-6967 Emergency Board #159 Issues: Rates of Pay; Rules; Retirement.
    - Railroads vs. Brotherhood of Railway Signalmen, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 19)
      4/3/1964; Expenses Incurred in Above Case.
    - Clippings, Memos, Correspondence, etc. Relating to the Above Case (Railroads vs. Brotherhood of Railway Signalmen)., 1964 (Box 114, Folder 20)
      4/3/1964
    - Rainbow Container Company vs. Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 1949 (Box 114, Folder 21)
      6/6/49; Issues: Termination of Employment; Medical Release.
    - Manhattan Rubber Division of Raybestos - Manhattan, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1679, 1957 (Box 115, Folder 1)
      1/29/1957; Issue: Reinstatement.
    - Raybestos - Manhattan Friction Materials Company vs. United Textile Workers of America, Local 2590, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
      5/17/1976; Grievance #90-75 Issue: Contracting Out.
    - Reeves Instrument Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 478, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 3)
      5/8/62; Issues: Termination of Employment; Standards of Production.
    - Remington Rand Company, Division of Sperry Rand Corporation, Tabulating Service Division vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Business Machine and Office Appliance Mechanics Conference Board, Local 459, 1956 (Box 115, Folder 4)
      9/11/56; Issues: Seniority; Promotions.
    - Republic Aviation Corporation., 1962 (Box 115, Folder 5)
      Contains a Report, a Final Report and an Addendum to the President by a Board of Inquiry Under Executive Orders #11025 and 11026, Concerning a Dispute Between Republic Aviation and Various of its Employees. The Dispute Was Settled, and the Addendum Writte
    - Republic Aviation Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 25, 1963 (Box 115, Folder 6)
      9/17/1963; #L-38846 NY-L-425-63 Issue: Union Representatives and Business.
    - Revere Copper and Brass Company, Division of Standard Rolling Mills vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 107, 1955 (Box 115, Folder 7)
      12/14/1955; Issues: Vacation Pay; Welfare Funds.
    - Revere Copper and Brass Company, Baltimore Tube Division vs. United Mine Workers of America, District 50 and Local 12999, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 8)
      12/11/1967; Issues: Discharge; Improper Work Practices; Improper Job Attitudes.
    - Reynolds Metal Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7098, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 9)
      6/2/69; #69A/6450 Resolved.
    - Richmond County News Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity., 1961 (Box 115, Folder 10)
      ca. 1/61; Withdrawn
    - The River Club of New York, Inc. vs. Hotel and Club Employees Union, Local 6, 1950 (Box 115, Folder 11)
      7/17/50; Issues: Arbitrability; Discharge; Insubordination.
    - John A. Roebling's Sons Division, Colorado Fuel and Iron Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1965 (Box 115, Folder 12)
      9/14/65; #L-46554 PHI-L-318-65 Grievance #RW-468 Issues: Transfers; Discrimination; Assignment of Jobs; Overtime.
    - Roebling Plant, Colorado Fuel and Iron Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2110, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 13)
      8/17/67; #14-30-0544-66 Grievance #R- 2460 Issue: Training and Trial Periods.
    - Roman Iron Works vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 445 1, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 14)
      1/30/1971; #1330-0556-71 Issue: Vacation Pay.
    - Rowe Manufacturing Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 950, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 15)
      12/21/1967; #1330-0932-66 Grievance #24-66 Issue: Bumping.
    - Royal Typewriter Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Royal Industrial Union, Local 937, 1956 (Box 115, Folder 16)
      2/23/1956; #L-15495 HART-L-112-55 Issue: Overtime.
    - Royal Wallpaper Company vs. Retail Clerks International Association, Local 1146, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 17)
      3/14/49; Issue: Holiday Pay.
    - Helena Rubinstein, Inc. vs. United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers Of America, Local 149, 1950 (Box 115, Folder 18)
      3/27/1950; #L-6067 NY-L-24-50 Issues: Reinstatement; Maternity Leave.
    - Safeway Trails, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 1112, 1965 (Box 115, Folder 19)
      6/25/1965; Issues: Arbitrability; Discharge.
    - St. Regis Paper Company, Panelyte Division vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 155, 1951 (Box 115, Folder 20)
      2/12/1951; Issues: Holiday Pay; Workweek.
    - St. Regis Paper Company, Panelyte Division vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 155, 1954 (Box 115, Folder 21)
      10/8/1954; Issue: Incentive Systems and Incentive Pay.
    - St. Regis Paper Company, Panelyte Division vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 155, 1958 (Box 115, Folder 22)
      2/7/58; Grievance #'s 2:57, 7:57, 13:57, 17:57, 17:57A Issues: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit; Contracting Out.
    - St. Regis Paper Company, Panelyte Division vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 155, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 23)
      1/29/1962; Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Schwerman Trucking Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 294, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 24)
      10/19/1975; Grievance #'s 1297, 1298 Withdrawn.
    - Scott Paper Company vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 1, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 25)
      4/20/1973; Issues: Bidding; Vacancies.
    - Seaboard Coal Dock Company vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Local 1463, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 1)
      10/19/1964; #L-41363 PHI-L-65-64 Issues: Hours of Work; Premium Pay.
    - Seaboard World Airlines, Inc. vs. Airline Mechanics and Stock Clerks and Seaboard World Airlines, Inc. vs. Traffic Agents and Cargo Servicemen, 1963 (Box 116, Folder 2)
      Unions represented by Transport Workers of America, Air Transport Division. 12/3/63. #M-19-62, and 12/7/63. #C-16-2 and C-17-62; Issues: Layoffs; Severance Pay.
    - Seaboard World Airlines, Inc., 1971 (Box 116, Folder 3)
      2/15/71; Withdrawn.
    - Shell Oil Company vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 8-800, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 4)
      6/8/70; Settled.
    - Short Line of Connecticut, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 1527, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 5)
      3/23/67; Settled.
    - Shulton, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 892, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      1/4/1967; Settled.
    - Simmons Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 315, 1954 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      4/9/1954; Issues: Layoffs; Vacation Pay.
    - Simplex Cloth Cutting Machines, Inc. vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 475, 1951 (Box 116, Folder 8)
      5/2/1951; Issues: Insurance; Vacation Pay; Rates of Pay.
    - Sonoco Products Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 271, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      1/6/1973; Grievance #'s 10, 15, 17, 18, 19 Case #71-628 Issues: Discharge; Improper Personal Conduct
    - South Oaks Hospital vs. Drug and Hospital Union Local 1199, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 10)
      2/4/74; Withdrawn.
    - Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company vs. Communications Workers of America, 1963 (Box 116, Folder 11)
      10/14/1963; Grievance #61-36-322 Issues: Discharge; Theft.
    - Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company vs. Communications Workers of America, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      9/23/1967; Grievance #63-15-343 Issues: Vacancies; Promotions; Seniority.
    - Southern New England Telephone Company vs. Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers, Inc., 1963 (Box 116, Folder 13)
      4/23/1963; #L-36601 HART-L-210-62 Issues: Rates of Pay; Transfers.
    - Spaulding Fire Company, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 2106, 1971 (Box 116, Folder 14)
      ca. 1971; Re Hill's Availability as Arbiter of the Above.
    - Sperry Gyroscope Company, Division of Sperry Rand Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 470, 1961 (Box 116, Folder 15)
      5/24/1961; Issues: Super seniority; Layoffs.
    - Sperry Gyroscope Company, Division of Sperry Rand Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 470, 1962 (Box 116, Folder 16)
      2/10/1962; Grievances S-229, S-236, S-274 Issues: Suspension; Transfers; Bidding.
    - Sperry Gyroscope Company, Division of Sperry Rand Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 445, 1962 (Box 116, Folder 17)
      12/8/1962; #L-34937 NY-L-404-62 Issue: Union Officials and Business.
    - Sperry Gyroscope Company, Division of Sperry Rand Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 470, 1963 (Box 116, Folder 18)
      12/7/1963; Grievance #'s 7281 and 7290 Issues: Bonuses; Shift Scheduling.
    - Sperry Gyroscope Company, Division of Sperry Rand Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Locals 450 and 470, 1966 (Box 116, Folder 19)
      5/18/66; Settled.
    - Sperry Division, Sperry Rand Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 20)
      10/8/1975; Grievance #75-248 Issue: Insurance.
    - Stainless Engineering and Machine Works vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 21)
      2/18/57; Issue: Rates of Pay.
    - A.E. Staley Manufacturing vs. Grain Millers Union, Local 234, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 22)
      5/23/1972; Issue: Schedules of Work.
    - Standard News Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 116, Folder 23)
      4/1/1960; Issues: Holidays; Holiday Pay.
    - Standard Motor Products, Inc., HyGrade Products Division vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 473, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 24)
      1/4/1949; Issues: Discharge; Union Representatives and Business.
    - Standard Motor Products, Inc. vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 188, 1961 (Box 116, Folder 25)
      6/10/61; Issue: Reporting Pay.
    - Stanley Tools Division of Stanley Works vs. Upholsterers International Union of North America, Local 465, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      7/14/75; Issues: Seniority; Layoffs.
    - D. Stein Dental Laboratory vs. Dental Technicians Equity, Local 201, FAECT, United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1949 (Box 117, Folder 2)
      12/6/1949; Issues: Layoffs; Recall.
    - Steinway and Sons vs. United Furniture Workers of America, Local 102, 1954 (Box 117, Folder 3)
      2/23/54; #L-11663-NY-L-523-53 Issue: Grievance Procedure.
    - Suffolk County vs. Suffolk County Civil Service Employees Association, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      10/13/1971; #71-104 Issue: Promotions.
    - Suffolk County vs. Suffolk County Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, Inc., 1973 (Box 117, Folder 5)
      11/2/1973; #73-114 Issue: Rates of Pay (Court Appearances).
    - Suffolk County Community College vs. Faculty Association of Suffolk Community College, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 6)
      8/27/1974; #73-128 Issues: Hiring; Part Time Employees.
    - Suffolk County Water Authority vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 393, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 7)
      10/20/1975; #1330-0561-75 Issues: Arbitrability; Promotion.
    - Sunrise Manor Nursing Home vs. Drug and Hospital Union, Local 1119, Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 8)
      11/8/74; #13-0021- 74 Issues: Rates of Pay; Shift Scheduling.